console it's the browsers built-in debugger you may have heard of it before
控制台它是浏览器的内置调试器，您之前可能听说过它，
but try running console log console it does a lot more than you may have
但尝试运行控制台日志控制台它所做的比您可能
realized in some cases you only want to console log something if a condition is
意识到的要多得多
false in that case you're probably looking for assert when the first
' 可能在第一个
argument is false it logs the second argument as an error
参数为 false 时寻找 assert 它将第二个参数记录为错误
another trick you'll often see people do is use console.log along with braces to
您经常会看到人们使用的另一个技巧是使用 console.log 和大括号来
provide labels for the things that they're logging that's cool in all but
为他们正在记录的内容提供标签，这很酷 总而言之，除了
change log to table and you get a much prettier output as j/s developers we
将日志更改为表格之外，作为 j/s 开发人员，我们
often like to abuse console and that can make things pretty messy use console
经常喜欢滥用控制台，这可能会使事情变得非常
group to group things together with a label then collapse them by default to
save space in the console things can also get ugly if you're logging a bunch
混乱 在控制台中，如果您正在记录
of objects changelog Tudor and you get a much cleaner triangle drop-down do you
一堆对象 changelog Tudor 并且您得到一个更清晰的三角形下拉列表，那么在控制台中的事情也会变得丑陋，如果是这样，您
ever find yourself manually incrementing a number in your console logs if so you
是否发现自己在控制台日志中手动增加了一个数字 您
might be able to save your sanity by using console count it takes an optional
可能可以通过使用控制台计数来节省您的理智，它需要一个可选
label and every time it's called it will increment the count by one on a similar
标签，每次调用它时，它都会在类似的注释上将计数增加一个
note you can also keep track of the amount of time between your console logs
您还可以跟踪控制台日志调用时间之间的
calling time will start a timer then time log will log the amount of time you
时间量 启动一个计时器，然后时间日志将记录您
elapsed since that timer started now in JavaScript we're often working in the
从该计时器启动以来经过的时间在JavaScript 中我们经常在
context of deeply nested functions and objects when debugging it may be
深度嵌套的函数和对象的上下文中工作调试时可能
necessary to traverse through the stack trace of your code use console trace in
需要遍历代码的堆栈跟踪 在
the function you would expect to be at the top of the call stack and now we can
您希望位于调用堆栈顶部的函数中使用控制台跟踪，现在我们可以
see exactly what happened before this function was pushed on to the top of the
确切地看到在此函数被推送到
call stack and lastly every good Jas developer should give their console logs
调用堆栈顶部之前发生了什么，最后每个优秀的 Jas开发人员都应该提供他们的控制台日志
some flair use % C as the first character in a string then pass in some
一些天赋使用 % C 作为字符串中的第一个字符，然后传入一些
CSS styling as your second argument and now the console is your canvas if you
CSS 样式作为第二个参数，如果你
want to see more short videos like this make sure to hit the like button thanks
想看到更多这样的短视频，现在控制台就是你的画布记得按赞
for watching and I will see you in the next one
谢谢收看，下期
you
再见